I would like to come, sir, please take a look at ICICI
Life, its gross direct premium, there has been an
upside of 38.6, which means that
approximately its market share has
increased by 35 basis points. What do you think should be done,
what kind of sentiment will be seen in it,
according to the chart, the stock seems to be
trading on the long side with a stop loss of 6,
and your target is 00 and 2000, yes,
and sir, please tell me its time frame once, tentatively it will
remain in the short term for a
month or two, and along with this, there
is current in the entire sector, ICC PR is also
going well, AC Line is also going well from below, there
is current in the entire sector, so if anyone
else wants to focus on other stocks, then
AL1 looks very good, sir,
okay, then you should keep an eye on HDFC Life as well, along with this,
we need to get information about AL1 Line.